You know there are all these resources out there if you do want to learn something
从人类语言到编程语言 如果我们想学习的话
from a like language in the world to a programming language.
有很多资源可以选择
I wonder if you have any advice for someone who
你是否有任何建议要提供给
really wants to learn more about say like deployment,
想要学习部署或 SageMaker
or SageMaker, or really building Machine Learning product end to end.
或从头到尾地构建机器学习产品的人
Right. I guess the key advice that I have is stay curious, stay hungry.
嗯我的核心建议就是保持好奇心 渴望学习 观察市场
Watch the market and the cool thing nowadays is that there's a lot of things online.
如今比较好的是网上有很多资源
So follow the key players especially folks that are investing in education, like Udacity,
可以关注行业领军者 例如像优达学城这样的教育机构
because besides getting information about a product,
因为除了可以了解产品
or a service, or technology,
服务或技术信息之外
you also get information about market dynamics,
还可以了解市场动态
about what are the technologies that are cool,
了解哪些技术比较酷
what are the people that are at the forefront of these technologies interested in.
大家都在关注什么样的前沿性技术
So then you can plan your trajectory of learning and then draw
这样就可以规划学习路径
your interests in a different types of products and
并对不同类型的产品
Machine Learning techniques that you want to learn.
以及机器学习技术产生兴趣
Stay curious and also just hop on the bandwagon of
要保持好奇心并利用在线教育资源
online education because there's a firehose out there of information.
因为外面的信息太多了
There's a lot of Machine Learning Algorithms,
有太多的机器学习算法
there's a lot of tools,
太多的工具
there's a lot of frameworks and it gets really
和太多的框架
confusing when you want to navigate bad ecosystem yourself.
如果自己去选择的话 很难定夺该选择什么
So it's very useful to work with an online learning tool that
所以很有必要选择一款在线学习工具
can guide you through the learning process and point you towards
这些工具可以不断引导你
some beacons that can really help you learn faster,
帮助你提高学习效率
and ignore the noise out there.
并忽略各种干扰因素
That's kind of part of the goal again that we have at SageMaker which is to bring
SageMaker 的目标也是这样
Machine Learning in front of the people that
使没有太多科学
particularly wouldn't have a science or engineering background,
或工程背景的人也能够
but could use Machine Learning.
使用机器学习技术
So the platform includes examples like we just
SageMaker 包含很多我们刚刚讨论过的示例
discussed that can guide people through really making Machine Learning useful.
可以指导学员掌握机器学习知识
So ignore the noise for a minute,
暂时忘记干扰
go through this specific example,
学习一个特定的示例
and then at the end of going through the example,
学完之后
you would have learned something useful, something practical,
可以掌握实用的知识
and you would have also learned a lot about Machine Learning theoretically.
并了解很多机器学习理论知识
So guided learning, staying curious,
有指导地学习 保持好奇心
watching the market and industry,
观察市场和行业
finding the key players in education and product development and product building,
寻找教育和产品开发及构建领域的领军者
getting to know their interests,
了解他们的兴趣
and then following that interest and trying to draw
然后根据这些兴趣
a roadmap for yourself that you can use for your next learning activities.
为自己制定一个学习计划并为下个学习活动提供指导
I agree. It's something where this field is changing so are the tools.
同意你的观点这个行业发展很快 不断出现很多工具
So as long as you keep on learning driven by your own interests and curiosity,
只要保持兴趣和好奇心
I think that's really the route to go.
就可以不断成长
I feel very lucky to work somewhere where I can partner
有幸能够与业内专家合作
with someone in industry because I really get to learn a lot.
我也学到了很多知识
So I want to thank you for joining us,
感谢你接受访谈
and just say hello to our students out there.
跟学员打个招呼吧
Thank you for having me,
感谢邀请我
and Machine Learning for the win.
通过机器学习取得成功
For the win.
取得成功